# Kulwant Singh Dhama



dhamaks@gmail.com



09887699988



linkedin.com/in/kulwant-singh-dhama-0b0764170

## Summary

I have experience Competitive Programming, Data Analytics, Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence and Google Cloud Plateform which makes me quite unique candidates for any job. I have a variety of skills that allows me to take any task. I have Greate Problem-solving skills with determination to my work.

## **Experience**



## Student Intern

Verzeo

Jun 2020 - Present (5 months +)

Verzeo is a pioneer in the Ed-Tech industry, the fastest-growing professional training platform in the country. As part of our initiative for educating the upcoming generations to be producers of technology.

## b Facilities Specialist

MyCaptain

Oct 2020 - Present (1 month +)

MyCaptain (www.mycaptain.in) is an Edu-Tech startup, previously incubated at IIM Bangalore and recognized by the United Nations SDSN as one of the Top 50 Worldwide Youth Solutions. We intend to help students discover and pursue their passions and make an informed career choice.

## **Ⅲ** Competitive Programmer

### HackerRank

Aug 2018 - Aug 2020 (2 years 1 month)

The experience as a competitive programmer at HackerRank was quite fun and acknowledging. Having experience as a competitive programmer gives me an edge in all the problem-solving tasks which require a wide understanding of algorithms and data structures.

URL - https://www.hackerrank.com/Walker\_2421

## **Virtual Industrial Training**

### Continental

Mar 2020 - Jun 2020 (4 months)

Complete a virtual industrial training at Continental Automotive Pvt. Ltd. under the supervision of Mr Arun Rohilla (Deputy Manager - NPL) in Industrial Engineering Department. During this period I have done a project on PY18 Renault line Installation.

### **Education**



## Shri Mata Vaishno Devi University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2018 - 2022

## **Licenses & Certifications**

30 Days of Google Cloud - Qwiklabs

https://www.qwiklabs.com/public\_profiles/3b1f4cfd-669d-479e-bb3d-3c0e2d3a49b6

- Google Cloud Platform Big Data and Machine Learning Fundamentals Coursera SPUAPKCR3TRQ
- R Programming Coursera
  GUTSJWNSKBYS
- R Programming A-Z™: R For Data Science With Real Exercises! Udemy UC-4962bc3f-02ff-4b15-b8e6-2547a903f7ce
- Python HackerRank 48749C898CBD
- Data Science: Foundations using R Specialization Coursera 944YHYVQKR9U
- Machine Learning Internshala
  9AE53C2C-E421-D678-F383-6A6CE22A4DA7
- Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure Coursera EJBA99BD53SJ

## **Skills**

C (Programming Language) • Databases • Python (Programming Language) • MySQL • Oracle SQL Developer • C# • C++ • R (Programming Language) • SQL • Problem Solving